{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/51623318","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51623318","name":"Ziggy's Bar & Grill","address":"16390-94 E. Warren Ave ","zipcode":"48224","owner":"Mr. Barnes","licenseNumber":"250442","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Temporarily Closed","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"335","coords":"-82.93787,42.40280","geojson":{"id":"51623318","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-82.937873707,42.402802609]},"properties":{"name":"Ziggy's Bar & Grill","owner":"Mr. Barnes","address":"16390-94 E. Warren Ave ","zipcode":"48224","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"250442","establishmentid":"51623318","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Temporarily Closed","review_frequency_days":"335","most_recent_license_date":"2021-09-07"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"797","name":"Ziggy's Bar & Grill","address":"16390-94 Warren E.","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51622845","name":"Flamzs","address":"16369 Warren E.","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51623573","name":"Morningside Cafe","address":"16369 Warren E.","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51624032","name":"Cloud Cafe","address":"16422 Warren Ave E.","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51622801","name":"Soul Food Shawarma","address":"16353 E. Warren","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"439","name":"Gino's Coney Island","address":"16353 Warren Ave. E.","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"1892","name":"Wine Basket","address":"16450 Warren Ave. E.","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"2333","name":"Club Xhale","address":"16314 Warren E.","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51623444","name":"The Warren Cafe","address":"16314 E. Warren","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51623669","name":"Terri's Cakes Detroit","address":"16311 Warren E.","zipcode":"48224"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"61132","inspectionDate":"2023-01-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"56406","inspectionDate":"2021-10-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not comply with law","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"At the Sanitizer","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-10-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"probe","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"No Digital Thermometer","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-11-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Equipment cobra head holders","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Beverage gun dispenser","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-201.16","violationDescription":"(A) Wall and ceiling covering materials shall be attached so that they are EASILY CLEANABLE.\n(B) Except in areas used only for dry storage, concrete, porous blocks, or bricks used for indoor wall construction shall be finished and SEALED to provide a SMOOTH, nonabsorbent, EASILY CLEANABLE surface.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wall/ceiling covering(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (MEN'S PUBLIC)","subLocation":"At the Ceiling tile(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Inside the Stove","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"No Management Certification Certificate","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"54569","inspectionDate":"2021-03-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"53156","inspectionDate":"2020-10-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"probe","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Thermometer(s)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-11-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Inside the Stove","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-205.10","violationDescription":"FOOD EQUIPMENT that is certified or classified for sanitation by an American National Standards Institute (ANSI)-accredited certification program is deemed to comply with Parts 4-1 and 4-2 of this chapter.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"At the Equipment","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"In prep area","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Missing Light Shield(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide adequate light shields and end caps or shatter-proof bulbs."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"ceiling","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Ceiling (s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Ventilation hood","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-205.10","violationDescription":"FOOD EQUIPMENT that is certified or classified for sanitation by an American National Standards Institute (ANSI)-accredited certification program is deemed to comply with Parts 4-1 and 4-2 of this chapter.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"At the Equipment","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Replace."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51623318"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}